Below freezing and beyond fear... Will anyone survive its terror?
Bear Island is a thriller, action, adventure film directed by Don Sharp.
A group of people converge on a barren Arctic island.
They have their reasons for being there but when a series of mysterious accidents and
murders take place, a whole lot of darker motives become apparent.
Could the fortune in buried Nazi gold be the key to the mystery?
Donald Sutherland and Vanessa Redgrave investigate
Frank Lansing, played by Donald Sutherland.
Heddi Lindquist, played by Vanessa Redgrave.
Otto Gerran, played by Richard Widmark.
Lechinski, played by Christopher Lee.
Judith Rubin, played by Barbara Parkins.
Smithy, played by Lloyd Bridges.
Bear Island is a 1979 adventure film based on Alistair
MacLean's 1971 novel of the same name.
It was directed by Don Sharp, and starring Donald Sutherland, Vanessa Redgrave,
Richard Widmark, Christopher Lee, Barbara Parkins and Lloyd Bridges.
The film explores themes of gold, island, based on
novel or book, nazi, professor.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.